Summary

Analytical web developer with several years of programming experience in a variety of different programming languages. Communicates proactively with team members and end users to streamline the process of building web applications.

Skills

- HTML/CSS/JS - NodeJS - Quick to Learn and Adapt

- JSON
- PHP/Laravel/MySQL
- Working with APIs
- TailWind
- Mongo DB
- Working in Teams
- Communication

Work Experience

May 2018 - Oct 2019 - 1 year 5 months

Cord Media, Palm Desert - Web Developer

- Attracted users to websites with professional, user-friendly designs and clean code for high-performance operation.
- Created highly responsive and scalable web applications for use in different industries and client environments.

June 2012 - June 2015 - 3 years

Envato, Tuts+, Remote - Assistant Tuts+ Web Dev Blog Editor, Staff Instructor

- Assisted writers in improving brand voice and core writing with direct coaching and mentoring for the Web Development Blog.
- Edited authors' first drafts, suggested additional content updates, and returned works to authors for review.
- Posted content online and updated landing pages, and resource pages, and wrote my own Web Development articles/videos.

Education

August 2008 - MONTH 2012

Franklin University, Ohio - Bachelor of Science in Web Development

Awards

Graduated with Honors; Cum Laude.